Yukako Yamagishi has been
feeling a bit crestfallen lately.
You have a crush on someone?
Yeah, and I think they
like me too! Really?
You'll never guess what happened
while I was at Angelo's Rock!
Tell us!
These tourists were taking
pictures and freaking out over it!
Who knew it would be such a hotspot?
Uh, Koichi? You okay?
As long as Koichi is in my
heart, that's all I need.
At least that's what I used to
think, until the pain set in.
If only he'd look at me,
even a glance would suffice.
I have no idea what I'm supposed to do.
Cinderella?
This is the best day ever!
I can't believe that Hang
Dreamboat actually proposed to me!
You're incredible, Dr. Aya!
Thank you so much for everything!
Her youth will be spent
as a cheerful troll.
Better that than a doleful beauty.
Oh, the things we endure.
Come in.
As you can see, our makeover
will help you find true love.
That's our personal guarantee.
Though the choice is yours.
This is Beauty Institute Cinderella.
Please don't be shy.
My name is Aya Tsuji.
I'm the principal owner and esthetician.
And don't worry, I'm not
as apathetic as I sound.
I'm actually very
passionate about my work.
Goodness.
You have such a lovely face. Gorgeous.
To think such a striking beauty was
hiding right here in little old Mariah.
Now then, come in and have a seat.
First, I'll need you to fill out
a form with your name and address.
Hold on, I haven't decided to go
through with whatever this is.
Of course, here's our list of services.
Marry a celebrity makeover?
My institute is a bit of a
departure from the mainstream.
You could describe my work as
constructing visages of good fortune.
One's physiognomy,
that is, the form of one's face, is
what essentially dictates one's luck.
Which means a face welcoming of love
increases your chances of finding love.
It's such a pity.
Your eyes and eyebrows were
cursed with an unlucky shape.
I'll be straight with you.
This was the shittiest
pitch I've ever heard.
You really charge for this crap?
With features like these, my dear,
the stronger your affection for a
boy, the harder he'll pull back.
Judging by your face, we've
reached the heart of the matter.
You're what's the matter.
That has never happened in my life.
Oh no?
You'll have to forgive me then.
At any rate, let's dive in.
Pardon the in-between stages.
I haven't quite mastered
computer graphics.
This is a face that will find true love.
Hang on a second.
Is this for plastic surgery?
Is that what you do here? No, dear.
I'll achieve this effect with
only makeup and a beauty massage.
But be aware you only have 30 minutes.
If you don't find love within that
time, I will refund your thousand yen.
Shall we give it a go?
Sure, but just the makeup.
I suppose I'll humor you this
once, but no funny business.
Much obliged.
Let's begin, shall we?
Now, please close your eyes.
Don't spoil the surprise by peeking, okay?
And whatever you do, stay perfectly still.
If you start wiggling around, my hands
could slip and we don't want that, do we?
Koichi...
Will this really help me find true love?
I just don't see how
changing the contours of
my eyes and eyebrows
could alter my chances.
Koichi?
I've been looking all
over town for you, Yukako.
Me?
Yeah.
Earlier, I saw you walking past Rengate.
You looked so down in the dumps
I got a little worried and...
Well, I thought I'd make
sure everything was okay.
Koichi.
Koichi, you really went out of
your way just to check on me?
Yeah, of course.
I know a lot has happened between us,
but that's all water under the bridge.
I sincerely want you to be happy. Really?
Do you mean that?
Yeah, I do.
I can't believe this is happening.
Could it be the makeup?
So, uh,
Koichi, instead of just
standing around here,
why don't we find a quiet place to chat?
Huh?
If you want, it's your decision.
You know, come to think of it, all that
searching has made me a little thirsty.
Huh? Really?
It's actually working.
Things are starting to change.
I'm sharing a table with my
adorable yet tenacious Koichi.
Though it's not the manliest choice.
It's incredibly manly.
I was thinking about
ordering the same thing.
It's like I'm dreaming that
physiognomy stuff works wonders.
I can feel it.
My luck is finally taking
a turn for the better.
Is this really happening?
I can feel his heartbeat,
the warmth of his body.
This must be what heaven feels like.
I've never been happier in my entire life.
Oh, look at the time.
It's already four.
What's going on?
Why does my stomach feel
like it's about to explode?
This isn't going to end well.
Sorry, Yukako.
I've got to go home right now!
Yukoichi, please don't!
It's not fair!
Why does it only last
for a measly 30 minutes?!
Damn it, lady!
Can't you see it's a red light?
Stuff it up your ass, douche!
It's not my fault the
frickin' light turned red.
Why does it only work
for a measly 30 minutes?
Do something to make it last longer!
You found love, didn't you?
Be happy with that for now.
You can come back to see me tomorrow.
That's what my other customers
do in cases like these.
Never!
A fate that rips me away from Koichi after
30 minutes is a fate I refuse to endure!
I want the win-your-soul-mate
treatment! Can you do it?
Graciousness isn't your
strong suit, is it?
Can you do it or not?!
Oh, dear Yukako,
Cinderella may have been mistreated,
but found true love because
she never lost her pure soul.
She's proof that fortune favors those who
keep an open mind and a willing heart.
Do you have the courage to do that?
A willing heart?
What does that mean?
If you truly wish to transform your luck,
it'll take more than mere
physiognomic alteration.
When I was a child,
I loved Cinderella's
fairy godmother so much
she inspired me to become an esthetician.
Like her, I'm dedicating my life to
the service of others by giving joy.
Yukako, you're the apple of my eye, so
I'll help to make your dream come true.
However, we'll need to include more
than just your face in the treatment.
Yes,
only a full body treatment will do,
so consider it part of the
Win Your Soulmate package.
Use this as an emblem of the
willing heart that beats within you.
Apply this lipstick every 30 minutes,
excluding the hours you're asleep, of course.
It preserves the potency of the treatment.
Maintain this ritual,
and you will have the chance to hold
on to your soulmate for eternity.
It's 72,000 yen for 24 hours.
Alright, let's just do it.
Very good.
Stay absolutely still.
Well, and be sure to keep those eyes shut.
Called it.
I knew you weren't some
ordinary beautician.
You have powers, and you can see
my Cinderella as well, can't you?
Now I get it.
You're a stand user like me.
But to be honest, I couldn't
care less about that.
If you were planning to eliminate me,
you would have done so a long time ago.
I trust you.
Work your magic, Fairy Godmother.
You startled me there.
That's nice.
Start the treatment.
Such a sublime girl.
Let's begin.
Know that you're in great hands.
Cinderella has the ability to
transform the body's appearance.
Its power gives my win-your-soul-mate
treatment that extra kick.
Yukako, dear.
Bathe in your new beauty as you
have become invincible in love.
This doesn't make any sense.
My stomach suddenly feels better.
What the heck?!
This is Yukako's bag!
Shoot, I have to hurry
and get it back to her!
Hi, Koichi.
Ya... Yukako...
Oh, yeah.
Before I forget, here.
Guess I must have picked
up your bag by mistake.
This one's mine.
The whole thing was my fault. I'm sorry.
Well, see you later!
Koichi, please don't run off just yet!
Look at me!
Really, look at me!
Don't I rouse any special
feeling in you? Any at all?
Well, you know, I think... maybe.
Would you look at that, it's Koichi.
Rohan-sensei!
I'm heading over to Kameyu to
do a little bit of research.
Do you want to keep me company?
I'd like to, but I
really need to head home.
I can't go around snapping
photos at the mall by myself.
What went wrong?
He's leaving!
Wasn't I supposed to become
an invincible heroine of love?
What happened to Cinderella's powers?
because right now this mission is a dud!
Rest assured, Koichi has already
fallen madly in love with you.
But his rational mind is
resisting his heart's impulses.
Did something happen between you two?
That might be the source of the problem.
Oh my!
Is this the manga artist?
It's wonderful to meet you.
Everything's going to be fine.
Soon enough, the tables
will turn in your favor.
Cinderella's power's absolute.
And so you know it's currently 4.45.
Your 30 minutes have almost expired.
It's imperative you remember
to apply the lipstick.
I know.
I'm putting it on now.
The tables are going to
turn in my favor, huh?
What?
You're going to Kama you?
Hey, that's funny, so are we! Huh?
What the hell's going on?
It's like a damn block party.
And to make matters even more
awkward, his mother is here!
The tables will turn in your favor.
My ass they will!
He'll butcher that
bullshitting beautician!
This seems like an
excellent place to start.
Sunny, you can't use
a flash near the baby.
This isn't good, Josuke.
The stress is triggering her
powers and she's disappearing.
Let's go, old man!
We gotta get out of here!
Our nest is coming through!
Move it, people!
Out of the way!
What's happening?
Sorry about that, Koichi!
Wowsers, Yukako...
Koichi...
She was right.
The tables have turned in my favor.
Our willing hearts beat as one, and our
souls are intertwined in a magical dance.
Nothing else matters
but us and this moment.
My new life begins now.
I can feel it.
Hey, Josuke, Okuyasu, don't freak.
But Yukako and I kind
of made out. So yeah.
Run that by me again?
What'd she do to you?
Are you going to have to
teach her another lesson?
Whoa, take it easy.
You've got it all wrong.
She didn't do anything.
If I'm being honest, I think
I've fallen for Yukako.
She's grown on me, and I get excited
thinking about spending time with her.
She makes me feel all warm and fuzzy.
Could this be love? I'm so confused.
Yo, are you catching all of this, Okuyasu?
This gushy stuff would
shock the pants off a stand.
Those two playing tongue hockey?
Pull it together.
It's weird, but it's nothing to cry about.
Anyway, Koichi,
I don't have the faintest clue as to what
spawned this stunning change of heart.
But hey,
if you and Yukako are really into each
other, then I wish you both the best of luck.
Thanks, but that's not the problem.
I don't know what's going on with
her, but she's refusing to see me.
It's all so baffling.
She's been absent from
school for two days.
She won't answer the phone
or say a single word.
She's off the grid, but how come?
Wow, so she went AWOL
after you guys kissed?
And you haven't talked to her since?
Not a word.
Uh-oh.
The silent treatment's a real bad sign.
It's a shame, too.
I admired her crazy devotion, but
ghosting you like this is so uncool.
It's gonna be awkward as hell,
but I think your best bet is asking
Yukako about it face-to-face.
I'm sorry, bud, but we
shouldn't get involved in this.
Yeah.
But if things turn ugly, give
us a holler and we'll rush over!
We'll be there to help before you know it!
Thanks, guys.
I'll see you both later.
See ya.
But still, damn that Koichi.
Why does he get to kiss a girl?
Calm down.
You're freaking out over nothing again.
I'd know that hair anywhere.
Yukako!
Please, wait up. We need to talk.
Yukako?
I'm sorry.
I don't know who you're referring to.
Oh, my mistake.
I saw your hair and thought
you were someone I know.
No!
I don't want you to go!
Oh, Koichi!
Why the hell would you do this
to me, you conniving trowel?
My face is falling apart and your stupid
makeup just cracks and flecks away!
Damn you!
You're a backstabbing bitch!
Turn my face back to normal!
Foolish girl.
Seems you didn't follow my instructions.
It's such a shame.
I truly thought I'd impressed
upon you the importance
of applying the Cinderella
lipstick every 30 minutes.
So this is my punishment for forgetting?
What is this? My hands!
What the hell is wrong with them?
The skin on my hands is breaking down!
Your palm lines and
fingerprints are disappearing.
That's what happens when
you don't follow orders.
That lipstick was an assurance of good
fortune during your quest for love.
Tremendous energy is required to
change the course of one's destiny.
And it's all used up.
You've only yourself to blame for
not taking your destiny seriously.
Hey, do you want to die?
Die, you say?
Ambition and wealth aren't my only
motivating factors, so save the intimidation.
I modeled myself after
the Fairy Godmother.
She was a sorceress of the highest
level and bringer of happiness.
It really is such a shame.
It's clear to me now that I never should
have tried to make your wish come true.
Your face and palms are long gone.
They've been erased from this world.
What did you say?
That they're gone.
And who has use for
things with missing parts?
My face.
It's gone forever.
This isn't fair.
How am I supposed to
live my life like this?
Yukako!
It's Koichi!
Why is he here?
I can't let him learn my secret!
No, I'm afraid not.
Sorry, but you've got the wrong person.
Dr.
Aya, your beauty institute
is for women only, correct?
I want him out of here now.
Nice try, but you can't fool me.
I'd know that tough as
Nils' temperament anywhere.
Now I know for sure you're Yukako.
Your personality leaves
a real strong impression.
And this lady, she's a
stand user, is that right?
From what I'm gathering,
she did something to you.
It's all over.
I can't live like this.
You'll pay for this, Aya Tsuji.
I'm gonna murder you!
Don't give in to despair.
What the hell?
Part of her face flew off and
is flying around the room!
There we go.
So this is Koichi.
He saw through your altered state
and identified you as Yukako.
You tried denying
yourself in front of him,
but some people just have
an eye for character.
All right, Yukako.
Out of consideration for
this young man's efforts,
I'll give you one final
chance as a fairy godmother.
Select one of these faces.
You have one chance, so choose wisely.
Know that your original face is no more.
But Cinderella remembers the
face of each patient that
has made use of its ability
and can replicate them.
Now, pick your own face
from among the samples.
If you can find it, there's a chance
your original features could be restored.
Your palms and fingerprints, too.
Much like Cinderella and
her famous glass slipper,
I invite you to find your perfect fit.
Why didn't you say that earlier, Dr.
Dumbass?
I'll be out of here in no time flat!
I look in the mirror every
day, so how hard can this be?
Don't get cocky.
If you choose someone else's face,
it'll clash with your own
as you might have imagined.
Actually, why sugarcoat the truth?
As an authority on all things beauty, I
can say your face will become grotesque.
No one will want to look at it.
What's more, the contours of your
face will dictate your destiny.
Hey, Yukako, be extra careful.
Remember, your face is reversed
when you look in a mirror.
Yeah, you're right.
Poor girl.
Truth is, none of the faces are correct.
Every one is a fake.
If you can figure that out,
I'll return your face to normal.
That is the fairy
godmother's rule. Damn it.
The more I look at them, the
more they look like my face.
But this is the one.
It has to be.
No way I'd be able to forget my own face.
You sure about that?
Once you try it on, you'll know for sure.
No, I'm wrong.
This isn't the right face.
I almost missed it, but my eyes
have more of a slant than these do.
Which one is it?
I have no idea!
What if I make the wrong decision?
What's wrong?
You have a face to
choose, so get to picking.
No, I won't.
I refuse to choose. But why?
So what are you saying?
You want to live out
your life without a face.
I'm saying I want Koichi to choose.
That way, it'll be a face Koichi can love.
I couldn't care less what it looks like!
And the amount of luck it has
doesn't mean a thing to me.
I'll bear with the outcome.
And live a life free of regret?
But what if I get it
wrong? What will you do?
I'll deal with it.
Please, Koichi!
For me.
Here, this is it.
I can't tell you why I chose it.
I guess it's just intuition.
But if I did mess up and
choose the wrong face...
Oh, by the way, this guy's
my stand, Reverb. Right.
So anyway, if I screw up, I want you to
wound Reverb's eyes and blind me for life.
I know you said you wouldn't have any
regrets, But knowing you like I do now,
you'd secretly get really
upset if I couldn't
see you just the way you've always been.
And though I couldn't see it
before, I'm in love with you.
I couldn't bear to see you unhappy.
That's why the best solution would
be for me to never see again.
Koichi.
Here, Yukako.
Right.
Look!
It's a perfect fit!
That's amazing!
Koichi!
Yeah, we did it, Yukako!
It's all because you were
brave enough to choose my face!
To think he'd sooner blind himself than
witness his beloved suffer unhappiness.
I figured as very godmother, I'd bend
the rules and give them a happy ending.
After all, if I stole the
eyesight of an innocent young man,
what kind of fairy godmother would I be?
You Kick dear, young as you are, you
have a keen eye for finding good men.
Beauty Institute Cinderella
is open for business.
Our makeovers will help
you find true love.